It's the last one you'll ever take.
Wrong Turn is a horror, thriller film directed by Rob Schmidt.
Chris crashes into a carload of other young people, and the group of stranded motorists is soon lost in the woods of West Virginia,
where they're hunted by three cannibalistic mountain men who are grossly disfigured by generations of inbreeding.
Jessie Burlingame, played by Eliza Dushku.
Chris Flynn, played by Desmond Harrington.
Carly, played by Emmanuelle Chriqui.
Scott, played by Jeremy Sisto.
Evan, played by Kevin Zegers.
Francine, played by Lindy Booth.
Wrong Turn is a 2003 slasher film directed by Rob Schmidt, written by Alan B.
McElroy, and starring Desmond Harrington, Eliza Dushku,
Emmanuelle Chriqui, Jeremy Sisto, and Kevin Zegers.
The first installment in the Wrong Turn film series, it follows a group of six individuals being
stalked by deformed, inbred, cannibalistic mountain men in the woods of West Virginia.
Development for the film began in 2001 when it was announced Summit Entertainment and Newmarket Group teamed to
produce Wrong Turn, a 1970s-style horror pic to be directed by Schmidt, while McElroy wrote the script.
The film was a co-production between Summit and Constantin Film, with Stan
Winston designing the creature effects and serving as a producer.
Wrong Turn was theatrically released in the United
States on May 30, 2003, by 20th Century Fox.
It grossed over $28 million worldwide against a $12 million budget
but received mixed-to-negative reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of life and death, loss of
loved one, job interview, mountain, gore.
The tone is dark and intense.